[
	{
		"front": "What nation won its first World Cup in 1998?",
		"back": "France" 
	},
	{
		"front": "What mononymous footballer famously headbutted an opponent in the 2006 World Cup?",
		"back": "Zidane"
	},
	{
		"front": "What is the name of the rivalry game played between Liverpool FC and Everton FC of the English Premier League?",
		"back": "Merseyside Derby"
	},
	{
		"front": "What country has won the most World Cup trophies?",
		"back": "Brazil"
	},
	{
		"front": "What football superstar said, 'Maybe they hate me because I'm too good'?",
		"back": "Ronaldo"
	},
	{
		"front": "What league is the highest division of professional soccer in the United States?",
		"back": "Major League Soccer"
	},
	{
		"front": "How many yellow cards constitute an ejection of a player from the game?",
		"back": "2"
	},
	{
		"front": "What woman has scored the most international goals in soccer?",
		"back": "Abby Wambach"
	},
	{
		"front": "Who is the highest-scoring male player in U.S. international soccer?",
		"back": "Landon Donovan"
	},
	{
		"front": "What is the name of world football's highest individual prize?",
		"back": "Ballon D'or"
	}
]